<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alexander Garbiak</title>
    <link>https://agarbiak.github.io/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://agarbiak.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Alexander Garbiak</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2020 Alexander Garbiak</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>img/map[gravatar:%!s(bool=false) shape:circle]</url>
      <title>Alexander Garbiak</title>
      <link>https://agarbiak.github.io/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://agarbiak.github.io/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://agarbiak.github.io/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Your privacy is important to me. It is my policy to respect your privacy regarding any information I may collect from you across my website, &lt;a href=&#34;http://garbiak.com&#34;&gt;garbiak.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I only ask for personal information when I truly need it to provide a service to you. I collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. I also let you know why I am collecting it and how it will be used.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data I store, I’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My website may link to external sites that are not operated by me. Please be aware that I have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are free to refuse my request for your personal information, with the understanding that I may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of my practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how I handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This policy is effective as of 28 January 2020.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;This privacy policy was based on a template by 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://getterms.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;GetTerms.io&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Use</title>
      <link>https://agarbiak.github.io/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://agarbiak.github.io/terms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;terms&#34;&gt;Terms&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By accessing the website at &lt;a href=&#34;http://garbiak.com&#34;&gt;garbiak.com&lt;/a&gt;, you are agreeing to be bound by these terms of service, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this website are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;disclaimer&#34;&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The materials on this website are provided on an &amp;lsquo;as is&amp;rsquo; basis. Alexander Gabiak, the website owner, makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties including, without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Further, Alexander Gabiak does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its website or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;limitations&#34;&gt;Limitations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In no event shall Alexander Gabiak be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on this website, even if Alexander Gabiak or an authorised representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;accuracy-of-materials&#34;&gt;Accuracy of materials&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The materials appearing on this website could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Alexander Gabiak does not warrant that any of the materials on its website are accurate, complete or current. Alexander Gabiak may make changes to the materials contained on its website at any time without notice. However Alexander Gabiak does not make any commitment to update the materials.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;links&#34;&gt;Links&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alexander Gabiak has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its website and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Alexander Gabiak of the site. Use of any such linked website is at the user&amp;rsquo;s own risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;modifications&#34;&gt;Modifications&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alexander Gabiak may revise these terms of service for its website at any time without notice. By using this website you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these terms of service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;governing-law&#34;&gt;Governing Law&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These terms and conditions are governed by and are to be interpreted in accordance with English law and in the event of any dispute arising in relation to these terms and conditions the English courts will have non-exclusive jurisdiction over such dispute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Terms of Use based on 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://getterms.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;GetTerms.io&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
